<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cassiel</title>
    <description>Cassiel: music, media, systems, performance, installation</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 12:24:33 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 12:24:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.2.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dotdotdot Dance: Blue Ghost</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After a two-year hiatus in development, all systems are go for Blue
Ghost, premiering in February 2023. Please see the &lt;a href=&quot;/project/blue-ghost&quot;&gt;project page&lt;/a&gt; for dates and details.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2022/12/17/blue-ghost/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2022/12/17/blue-ghost/</guid>
        
        <category>blue-ghost</category>
        
        <category>dotdotdot</category>
        
        <category>dance</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Choregraphic Coding Lab 14</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We’ve just wrapped from facilitating at the 14th &lt;a href=&quot;https://choreographiccoding.org&quot;&gt;Choreographic Coding Lab&lt;/a&gt; at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aoiesteban.com/aecreativehub/about&quot;&gt;A+E Lab&lt;/a&gt; in Chatham. This is the first CCL to be hosted in the UK, and marks 8 years since we attended CCL in Berlin. Over the last eight years, machine learning and game engines have definitely become a thing. However, I did find myself revisiting Clojure &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/clojure/core.logic&quot;&gt;core.logic&lt;/a&gt;, which I last explored in 2014. There is definitely more pntential in “old school” AI techniques like logic programming and theorem proving, as currently being explored by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.georgicapettus.com/&quot;&gt;Georgica Pettus&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2022/07/09/ccl-14/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2022/07/09/ccl-14/</guid>
        
        <category>ccl</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Darwin Grosse 1959-2022</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am greatly saddened by the death of Darwin Grosse. He and I had been friends for the best part of three decades; he mastered my first album &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/01/21/listen-move-bandcamp/&quot;&gt;Listen/Move&lt;/a&gt; back in 1996 or so, engaged me as a freelancer working for &lt;a href=&quot;https://cycling74.com/&quot;&gt;Cycling ‘74&lt;/a&gt; a couple of times, and he was responsible for landing me what I usually refer to as the “gig from hell” in Hollywood around 2004. Darwin oversaw that project (or at least, the involvement of myself and a small development team) and kept things on the road through numerous obstacles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Darwin has been an immensely supportive and positive figure in the experimental electronic music scene for many years, through his work for Cycling ‘74, his &lt;a href=&quot;https://artmusictech.libsyn.com/&quot;&gt;Art + Music + Technology podcast&lt;/a&gt; dating from 2013 (he and I spoke way back in &lt;a href=&quot;https://artmusictech.libsyn.com/podcast-009-nick-rothwell&quot;&gt;Episode 009&lt;/a&gt;), and through articles, interviews, tutorials, meet-ups and conversations too numerous to mention. He will be sorely missed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A couple of good obituaries:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.synthtopia.com/content/2022/06/06/composer-developer-podcaster-darwin-grosse-has-died/&quot;&gt;Synthtopia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cdm.link/2022/06/darwin-grosse-musical-visionary-and-voice-for-max-and-diy-learning-has-passed-away/&quot;&gt;CDM&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;charity-donation&quot;&gt;Charity Donation&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After discussion with Darwin’s family I’ve decided to donate all proceeds from sales of Listen/Move, in perpetuity, to cancer charities (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cancerresearchuk.org/&quot;&gt;Cancer Research UK&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.macmillan.org.uk/&quot;&gt;Macmillan Cancer Support&lt;/a&gt;). The two timeline tracks from Listen/Move are available here:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe style=&quot;border: 0; width: 100%; height: 120px;&quot; src=&quot;https://bandcamp.com/EmbeddedPlayer/track=3898512507/size=large/bgcol=ffffff/linkcol=0687f5/tracklist=false/artwork=small/transparent=true/&quot; seamless=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cassiel.bandcamp.com/track/listen-move-timeline-1&quot;&gt;Listen/Move: Timeline 1 by cassiel&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;iframe style=&quot;border: 0; width: 100%; height: 120px;&quot; src=&quot;https://bandcamp.com/EmbeddedPlayer/track=3705393383/size=large/bgcol=ffffff/linkcol=0687f5/tracklist=false/artwork=small/transparent=true/&quot; seamless=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cassiel.bandcamp.com/track/listen-move-timeline-1&quot;&gt;Listen/Move: Timeline 2 by cassiel&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/iframe&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2022/06/10/darwin-grosse-1959-2022/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2022/06/10/darwin-grosse-1959-2022/</guid>
        
        <category>darwin-grosse</category>
        
        <category>cycling-74</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Vangelis 1943-2022</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;To describe Vangelis as “unique” is an incredible understatement. He came to prominence (in the UK at least) at a time when the electronic music scene was dominated by French and German musicians, with a genre and aesthetic largely in common. Vangelis swept in from Greece with a style that was symphonic, pastoral, jazzy, and above all expressive. With acoustic orchestral percussion featuring prominently, his work never struck me as wholly “electronic”, and from an EM point of view his timbral palette tended to be limited. But within those limits, his material was immensely musical, heartfelt and, in places, joyously bombastic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe style=&quot;border-radius:12px&quot; src=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/embed/album/6Tz3gRyPvHv8eDT5RZ2xXX?utm_source=generator&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;380&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel his strongest work is from the “RCA Years”: Heaven and Hell, Albedo 0.39, Spiral. The mixes are a little rough, but full of energy, and show off the Yamaha CS-80 to full effect. The more experimental Beaubourg should be included as well, and I happen to love it, whether or not it was quickly improvised to a tight deadline. For a bit more polish, try China (which, for audiophiles, was issued by Polydor who pressed on better vinyl than RCA).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe style=&quot;border-radius:12px&quot; src=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/embed/album/3UNXsFe9kpKxRaKE1hG7TD?utm_source=generator&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;380&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My favourite Vangelis works actually lie a little out of the main catalogue. Unlike, oh, let’s say Tangerine Dream, his film soundtracks were pretty uniformly excellent. I adore Le Singe Bleu from Apocalypse des Animaux, as well as most of Opera Sauvage and the first half of Ignacio. Blade Runner is an excellent, moody mix of music and sound design, inseparable from the movie. Some works (The Bounty, 1492: Conquest of Paradise) I find a little weaker, since they seem to veer a little into standard Hollywood structures and arrangements. And I’ll place myself in an absolute minority here by saying that I’m not over-fond of Chariots of Fire: I find it slightly anodyne.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe style=&quot;border-radius:12px&quot; src=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/embed/album/500swsVDu1EWuGohjXvago?utm_source=generator&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;380&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Around the mid-1980s Vangelis seemed to abandon the analogue instruments that gave him such expressive freedom and shifted into a more preset world, with sampled guitar and strings. Soil Festivities is perhaps the last of the great works, coming out during that transition (and maybe I’d add Mask as well). There’s still compositional flair and skill in The City and Direct, but by the time we get to Mythodea and El Greco, things seem a little flat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s very possible that I’m being over-critical, or am inordinately attached to a particular early part of his career; I have El Greco playing right now and it’s a finely crafted piece, but compared to the creative madness of tracks like Pulstar, The Dragon, See You Later and Needles &amp;amp; Bones, the later works feel weak.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, as such a musical force of nature (and even if only a fraction of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.soundonsound.com/news/vangelis-1943-2022-obituary&quot;&gt;Paul Wiffen’s Sound On Sound obituary&lt;/a&gt; is true), Vangelis will be sorely missed.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2022/05/28/vangelis-1943-2022/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2022/05/28/vangelis-1943-2022/</guid>
        
        <category>vangelis</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Klaus Schulze 1947-2022</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;As a teenager I felt a certain degree of pride in being a Klaus Schulze fan. His work was hard to find in record shops, and he didn’t get radio airplay (even on those European radio stations that were sometimes accessible on the shortwave band after dark), which meant that one often had to buy his LPs unheard. And the listening could be a challenge: tracks of 30 minutes duration, which meant narrower grooves on an LP, not ideal when pressed by Island UK who were notorious for using sub-standard cast-off vinyl from their classical releases.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe style=&quot;border-radius:12px&quot; src=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/embed/album/4QNKVVSKtnWETW17gzihFu?utm_source=generator&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;380&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m pretty sure my first purchase was Mirage, and on first listening it seemed pretty opaque: 30 minutes of Moog-filtered noise on side 1, and a relentless sequenced pattern on side 2. I might have given up at that stage, but I came across a compilation LP called Brainwaves featuring various artists from the German Brain label, and this featured a short extract of a Schulze track called Stardancer: dynamic, melodic, percussive. That was enough to persuade me to give Schulze another go, and eventually I discovered the full-length version of Stardancer on the Body Love soundtrack. It’s one of many tracks which evidence Schulze’s skills as an improvisational keyboard soloist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I had accidentally stumbled into Schulze’s creative peak, although many folk will argue that earlier works such as Blackdance and Timewind (or even Cyborg) should feature. For me, many repeated listenings to Mirage caused it to open and unfold into a truly deep, expansive and contemplative experience, and 40 years on I still find it incredibly immersive and rewarding. It is hard to overestimate its impact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe style=&quot;border-radius:12px&quot; src=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/embed/album/4M8LtVeYa55bP7jkKvFrx9?utm_source=generator&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;380&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of his other work of the period, the double album “X” is also strong and immersive, particularly the futuristic track Heinrich von Kleist, and the title track of the Dune album is a masterful piece of composition, with a beautiful reverberant but contained atmosphere. (Both Heinrich von Kleist and Dune heavily feature the Eventide harmoniser, which saw brief popularity in the late 1970s - see also Tangerine Dream’s Force Majeure.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe style=&quot;border-radius:12px&quot; src=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/embed/album/62jy0gLKN5x0VoHP4ZJsu9?utm_source=generator&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;380&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The shift from analogue to digital instruments and production in the mid 1980s affected Schulze strongly, and he seemed to shift away from immersive atmospherics and into sampled collage. He was incredibly prolific in the digital age, to a fault: some 40 albums plus numerous boxed set collections, editions and works. In my opinion, most are weak and even verge on unlistenable, but there are some gems, usually when Schulze veers back into the analogue domain: the “Dark Side of the Moog” collaborations with Pete Namlook are generally presentable and, in places, really good, as is much of the work with Lisa Gerrard. And to be fair, some of his “digital” albums such as Audentity and Trancefer are strong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have been long frustrated with this apparent emphasis on quantity rather than quality (telegraphed, in fact, by the sleeve notes in Mirage) but there’s enough superb work in his catalogue to make Klaus Schulze an incredibly important figure in electronic music, and a great loss.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2022/05/01/klaus-schulze-1947-2022/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2022/05/01/klaus-schulze-1947-2022/</guid>
        
        <category>klaus-schulze</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Audio Damage Other Desert Cities</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Review: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.audiodamage.com/collections/software/products/ad054-other-desert-cities&quot;&gt;Other Desert Cities&lt;/a&gt; in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.soundonsound.com/reviews/audio-damage-other-desert-cities&quot;&gt;Sound On Sound&lt;/a&gt;, February 2022.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2022/02/05/audio-damage-other-desert-cities/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2022/02/05/audio-damage-other-desert-cities/</guid>
        
        <category>sound-on-sound</category>
        
        <category>audio-damage</category>
        
        <category>review</category>
        
        <category>article</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Listen/Move on Bandcamp</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s been a long time coming, but we finally have Listen/Move on Bandcamp. It’s divided into its two timelines, which was always the original intended structure, loosely envisaged as “journey” and “destination”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cassiel.bandcamp.com/track/listen-move-timeline-1&quot;&gt;Timeline 1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cassiel.bandcamp.com/track/listen-move-timeline-2&quot;&gt;Timeline 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The artwork for the timelines is scanned from the two CD pressing runs, the first for &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theplace.org.uk/&quot;&gt;The Place&lt;/a&gt; Dance Theatre in London, the second for general release.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Longer term, the plan is to release a series of 30-minute-or-so “übertracks” as a follow-on from the &lt;a href=&quot;/project/minute-cubes/&quot;&gt;Minute Cubes&lt;/a&gt;. Listen/Move is the launch vehicle for those.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-lg-8 col-lg-offset-2 col-md-10 col-md-offset-1&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;block-image&quot;&gt;
      &lt;!-- Retrofit: deal with project in-page images as well as posts: --&gt;
      

      
        &lt;div class=&quot;image-area&quot;&gt;
          &lt;div class=&quot;overlay&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
          &lt;a href=&quot;
          /img/2022/01/body/lm-1-bandcamp.jpg
        &quot; data-lightbox=&quot;_&quot; data-title=&quot;Edition 1 with Jane Howie&quot;&gt;
            &lt;img src=&quot;
          /img/2022/01/body/lm-1-bandcamp.jpg
        &quot; alt=&quot;Edition 1 with Jane Howie&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2022/01/21/listen-move-bandcamp/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2022/01/21/listen-move-bandcamp/</guid>
        
        <category>bandcamp</category>
        
        <category>listen-move</category>
        
        <category>ubertracks</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Let Them Eat Cake!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Let Them Eat Cake! is a dance film on girl empowerment, where three teenagers rebel against how society dictates how they see themselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It will be directed by the choreographer and filmmaker Avatâra Ayuso, whose latest film &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/12/18/the-protocol/&quot;&gt;The Protocol&lt;/a&gt; has received awards all around the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.crowdfunder.co.uk/let-them-eat-cake-dance-film-on-girl-empowerment&quot;&gt;support a good cause&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2021/11/21/let-them-eat-cake/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2021/11/21/let-them-eat-cake/</guid>
        
        <category>dance</category>
        
        <category>ava-dance</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Donate Yourself</title>
        <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Donate Yourself is a new work – an Augmented Reality experience created by artist Stacey Pitsillides with body&amp;gt;data&amp;gt;space. It blends sound and 3D visuals to spark debates about our organs, tissue and body data, accessed by the public through augmented reality via QR codes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Find out more about the project and how to access the AR experiences &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.onecellatatime.org/exhibits/donate-yourself/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Donate Yourself by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bodydataspace.net/who-we-are/stacey/&quot;&gt;Stacey Pitsillides&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bodydataspace.net/&quot;&gt;body&amp;gt;data&amp;gt;space&lt;/a&gt; (2021). A One Cell at a Time commission with the Human Cell Atlas research initiative:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Designed and creatively directed by Stacey Pitsillides in collaboration with the interaction design collective body&amp;gt;data&amp;gt;space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The digital AR experience has been co-created with the body&amp;gt;data&amp;gt;space team using the b&amp;gt;d&amp;gt;s AR development project: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bodydataspace.net/who-we-are/core-team/ghislaine/&quot;&gt;Ghislaine Boddington&lt;/a&gt; (Creative Co-Direction), &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bodydataspace.net/who-we-are/core-team/tadej/&quot;&gt;Tadej Vindis&lt;/a&gt; (Project Development and Production), &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bodydataspace.net/who-we-are/core-team/nick/&quot;&gt;Nick Rothwell&lt;/a&gt; (Sound Design and Technical Development) and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bodydataspace.net/who-we-are/associate/ivor/&quot;&gt;Ivor Diosi&lt;/a&gt; (AR Development and 3D Animation). With research and insights from Holly Standing and Luke Sellers. Donate Yourself is produced for One Cell at a Time by Dominic Smith.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Donate Yourself is created as part of the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bodydataspace.net/2020/12/research-development-project-launch-datum/&quot;&gt;AR gifting development project&lt;/a&gt; at body&amp;gt;data&amp;gt;space, supported by Innovate UK and the University of Greenwich (2021-22).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One Cell at a Time is a programme of public, creative engagement activities, commissions and talks, inspired by the Human Cell Atlas, bringing together arts and communities, patients and researchers. Funded by Wellcome and led by the Wellcome Sanger Institute, One Cell at a Time aims to deepen public understanding of the revolutionary impact it will have on our understanding of the human body.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Special thanks to XR.+ by The Lucid Dreams Company, and TL Multimedia Ltd.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2021/11/07/donate-yourself/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2021/11/07/donate-yourself/</guid>
        
        <category>body-data-space</category>
        
        <category>wellcome</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bitwig Studio 4 Review</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Review: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bitwig.com/overview/&quot;&gt;Bitwig Studio 4&lt;/a&gt; in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.soundonsound.com/reviews/bitwig-studio-4&quot;&gt;Sound On Sound&lt;/a&gt;, November 2021.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2021/11/06/bitwig-studio-4/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2021/11/06/bitwig-studio-4/</guid>
        
        <category>sound-on-sound</category>
        
        <category>bitwig</category>
        
        <category>review</category>
        
        <category>article</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
